ILR School Dean's Office Files Additional /4144
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- G-1-2 Applicants O-S 1959 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- G-1-2 Applicants T-Z 1958-'59, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- G-1-2 A-B 1956-'57, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  Includes some Italian language material; includes several memos from late 1955
- G-1-2 A-B 1956-'57 continued, 1946-1957 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  Includes a memo from late 1955 and a probably misfiled memo from 1946
- G-1-2 C 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- G-1-2 C 1956-'57 continued, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- G-1-2 D 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- G-1-2 E-F 1956-'57, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  Includes several memos from late 1955
- G-1-2 G 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- G-1-2 H 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- G-1-2 H 1956-'57 continued, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  One letter is attached to a report published in 1955
- G-1-2 I,J,K 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Includes a black and white photograph
- G-1-2 L 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- G-1-2 Mac, Mc, M1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- G-1-2 Mac, Mc, M 1956-'57 continued, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- G-1-2 N, O, P 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Includes several black and white photographs
- G-1-2 Q-R 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- G-1-2 S 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- G-1-2 T 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- G-1-2 U-V 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- G-1-2 W 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- G-1-2 X, Y, Z 1955-'57, 1955-1957 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- G-1-2 Correspondence A-C 1957-'59, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- G-1-2 Correspondence A-C 1958-'59, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- G-1-2 Correspondence D-F 1958-'59, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- G-1-2 Correspondence G-J 1958-'59, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- G-1-2 Correspondence K-M 1958-'59, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- G-1-2 Correspondence N-Q 1958-'59, 1957-1959 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  Includes several letters from late 1957
- G-1-2 Correspondence N-Q 1958-'59 continued (Box 13, Folder 18)
- G-1-2 Correspondence R-S 1958-'59, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- G-1-2 Correspondence T-Z 1957-'60, 1957-1960 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- G-1-2 Solo Applicants A-J 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- G-1-2 Job Applicants M-Z 1957 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- G-1-2 Labor Extension 1947-'48, 1947-1948 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  Includes selections from the Congressional Record
- G-1-2 Labor Extension 1948-'51, 1948-1951 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  Includes news clippings and selections from the Congressional Record
- G-1-2 Labor Extension Bill 1948-'51 (continued), 1948-1951 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- G-2-1 Applicants to Other Schools and/or Colleges 1958-'59, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Institute of International Industrial and Labor Relations (1951-1952) I (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Institute of International Industrial and Labor Relations (1951-1952) II (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Institute of International Industrial and Labor Relations (1951-1954) III (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Institute of International Industrial and Labor Relations (1955-1958) IV (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Chilean Project files I, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Chilean Project files II, 1960-1962 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Includes some Spanish language material; includes news clippings
- Chilean Project files III, 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Chilean Project files IV, 1958-1962 (Box 14, Folder 8)